"text","label"
"R.H. Saunders ( St. Lawrence River ) ( 968 MW )","B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O"
"; ' '' Anders Lindström '' '","O O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Karl Ove Knausgård ( born 1968 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Atlantic City , New Jersey","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Her daughter from the second marriage was Marie d'Agoult ( 1805–1876 ) , who in turn gave birth to several children , among them—from her liaison to Franz Liszt –- Cosima Wagner ( 1837–1930 ) .","O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"St. Mary 's Catholic Church ( Sandusky , Ohio )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Shhh ... Do n't Tell ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Antonín Rýgr ( 1970–72 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Dia Evtimova Catalina Castaño Dinah Pfizenmaier Tatjana Malek","B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER"
"102.7 MHz Triple J – ABC","O O B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG"
"*20px Idaho State Highway 5","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' Atelocentra '' Meyrick , 1884","O B-LOC O O O O"
"' '' Antarctic prion '' '","O O B-LOC I-LOC O O"
"James Franco ( M.F.A .","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Civic Freedom Party","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"キイロキリガ — Xanthia togata '' ( Esper , 1788 )","O O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"*August 8 – Craig Breslow","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"He has also won the Japan Senior Open twice .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"His great-grandson is director Whit Stillman .","O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"'' ' '' Chauliodus '' ' ''","O O O B-ORG O O O"
"Janaki]] , S. P. Balasubrahmanyam","O O B-PER I-PER I-PER"
": ' '' Thornhill Islanders '' ' defeated Markham Waxers ''4-games-to-3 ''","O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Obituary of Juliette Peirce .","O O B-PER I-PER O"
"78 '' in Osnabrück .","O O O B-LOC O"
"Gian Girolamo Albani","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"`` Rhinestone Cowboy '' ( Larry Weiss ) - 3:15","O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"*Episode 9 - Michael Conlan","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"Antawn Jamison ( 28 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Chillicothe Paints ( 1993–2008 , joined the Prospect League )","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"Antoine Dadin de Hauteserre","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"1978 demo released on Off the Wall ( Special Edition ) '' ( 2001 )","O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"Eveno-Bytantaysky National District","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Euxoa centralis '' ( Staudinger , 1889 )","O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O"
"Diocese of San Andrés Tuxtla","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Palisades , New York","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Rosephanye Powell ( born 1962 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Chum Ta Bong District","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Epica – Consign to Oblivion ''","B-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"'' Epirrhoe rivata '' ( Hübner , 1813 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"** '' Justice League Elite '' :","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"It is found in Peru .","O O O O B-LOC O"
"** Ecuador : 7 % of the population","O B-LOC O O O O O O"
"Translator of KCCV-FM , Overland Park , Kansas","O O B-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Mrs Brigitte Vallée .","O B-PER I-PER O"
"Lipiny , Ciechanów County","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Tatiana Volosozhar / Maxim Trankov","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Raymerville – Markville East , Ontario","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Robert Maxwell , 5th Lord Maxwell ( 1493–1546 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Prince Rupert of the Rhine 15 August 1672 – 19 November 1682","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O O O"
"Železničná spoločnosť Slovensko","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"On February 6 , 1925 he retired from active duty and died in Santiago in 1938 .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-LOC O O O"
"The 67 's finished in last place in the 2012–13 OHL season with just 16 wins .","O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O"
"Internet Exchange Point ( IXP )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"It was released as the first single from their 2004 album Everybody Loves a Happy Ending '' and is the first single that features both original members Roland Orzabal and Curt Smith since 1990 .","O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Conservative]] Leader David Cameron )","O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Much of the story takes place in Flagstaff , Arizona , where Sgt .","O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"'' Invisible Touch '' – Genesis","O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG"
"United States Senate Librarian","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Live at Sin-é ( Legacy Edition ) ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"' '' Calgary '' ' , ' '' Canada '' '","O O B-LOC O O O O O B-LOC O O"
"*2001 – Hugh Hefner , Roastmaster Jimmy Kimmel","O O B-PER I-PER O O B-PER I-PER"
"Aigle Noir AC","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Hathaways Mountain Pines , California","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Peter T. King","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Charlie Clouser – Nine Inch Nails","B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Former collegiate church St Bartholomew , Liège","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC"
"Zlaté Moravce District","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Wilhelm Gustav Franz Herter","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Thomasville , Missouri","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Clement Poitrenaud , 14 .","B-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Yahn | Yazdan Chah | Yegi | Yekkeh Derakht | Yosht | Yusefabad | Yush | Yushu","B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC"
"1982 Tour de France","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"John Denison-Pender , 1st Baron Pender","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"'' Glyphipterix iometalla '' ( Meyrick , 1880 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"'' Zygaena cynarae '' ( Esper , 1789 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"'' Super World of Sports '' '","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Chananel ben Chushiel","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Bobby Rush ( D )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Legend of Chun Hyang ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"BBC ( Test Match Special '' )","B-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Bruce Beresford ( Non-Jew )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"It was also released along with Visual Studio 2005 , Microsoft SQL Server 2005 , and BizTalk 2006 .","O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG O O"
"Leonardo Rodríguez Solís","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"She was born in Aldsworth , Gloucestershire , England on 10 January 1836 .","O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O O O O O"
"** Kyoto National Museum ( early production cast )","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O"
"List of years in Brazil","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"It is found in Mexico , Guatemala , Costa Rica , Panama , Colombia , Venezuela and Brazil .","O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O"
"' '' Michele Morosini '' ' ( 1308–1382 ) was ''doge '' from June 1382 until his death in October of the same year .","O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"20px Władysław I the Elbow-high","O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Misawa AB , Japan , 29 November 1965 – 15 May 1971","B-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O O O O O O O O"
"Flatnose xenocongrid eel","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"He resigned in March 1906 to run for West Hobart , but was unsuccessful .","O O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O"
"Lăpugiu de Jos","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Chinantec of Ozumacín","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"*October 4 – Drew Stubbs","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"16th Troop Carrier Squadron : attached 14 November 1954 – 8 July 1955","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O"
"File : Bdg fontannaPotop 2 10-2013.jpg|View from the foutain `` Deluge ''","O O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"It was described by Warren in 1892 .","O O O O B-PER O O O"
"Varghese Payyappilly Palakkappilly","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"It sold 184,000 in traditional album sales ( down 65 percent ) and was beaten to the top by Adele 's 25 '' , which debuted at number one with a record-breaking 3.38 million .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-PER O B-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"He was born in in Sundridge , Ontario .","O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Super League Greece : 1982–83","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG"
"Guy Berryman ( Coldplay )","B-PER I-PER O B-ORG O"
"Jason Schwartzman , Isabelle Huppert , Dustin Hoffman","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"' '' Lena Springs '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"He is a former England under-21 international .","O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Clement of Alexandria , ''Stromata '' 1.131.6 .","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Human Rights Commission of Malaysia","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"The elevation is 3944 feet ( 1202 m ) above sea level .","O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Jean Frédéric Frenet","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"** '' Duchy of Naples '' ' – Gregory III ( 864–870 )","O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Poland in the Eurovision Song Contest","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Space Heater ( album ) ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Thompson International Speedway – Thompson , Connecticut","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Recorded at Alberts Studio , London .","O O B-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O"
"West Herzegovina Canton","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Ili Kazakh Autonomous Prefecture","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"**London : Thames & Hudson .","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Takht Sri Hazur Sahib , Nanded","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC"
"lifebelt]]s that survived the sinking is on display at the Imperial War Museum North in Manchester","O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC"
"His father was Abd Manaf ibn Qusai .","O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O"
"Borg El Arab Stadium , Alexandria , Egypt","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O B-LOC"
"`` A Different Corner ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"1283 : The Yuan Dynasty claim possession of the Penghu Islands","O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-ORG I-ORG"
"Alain Delon , Richard Conte , Carla Gravina","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"**Monarch - George V , King of the United Kingdom ( 1910–1936 )","O O B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Helene Hayman , Baroness Hayman","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"`` You 're the Voice ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"A few months later two planes , one of them named ''Atlântico '' , were sent by ship to Montevideo and flown to Buenos Aires .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-LOC O O O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"New York State Route 5","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Des pères , des hommes et des frères","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Before 1945 the area was part of Germany .","O O O O O O O B-LOC O"
"5000-meter run – 14:15.61 ( 2015 )","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O"
"Sridevi , Sanjay Dutt , Rahul Roy","B-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Miranda Martino as the Singer","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Communist Party of Nigeria ( CPN )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"** '' Chaetodon falcula '' , Blackwedged butterflyfish","O O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-LOC I-LOC"
"The first settlers arrived in the early 19th century , and were largely Quakers , Mennonites and United Empire Loyalists who had left the United States .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG O B-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"Republic of Ezo ( 1868–1869 )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"Hul , Nové Zámky District","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Estadio Tiburcio Carías Andino Tegucigalpa , Honduras","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG B-LOC O B-LOC"
"Bokówka , Podlaskie Voivodeship","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Robert A. Borski , Jr .","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Perry Township , Fayette County , Ohio","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Tsardom of Russia '' ' – Feodor III ( 1676–1682 )","O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"St George 's , University of London ( SGUL )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Wales national football team","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"*wisent ( Bison bonasus '' )","O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Warrandyte South , Victoria","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Prochoreutis stellaris '' ( Zeller , 1847 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"UEFA Cup winner 1981 .","B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG O"
"In 1926 he was promoted to the rank of Marshal of Italy .","O O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O"
"Her grandson Stanley Eric Francis Booth-Clibborn became the Anglican Bishop of Manchester .","O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O B-ORG B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"It will serve the suburb of Murrumba Downs in the Moreton Bay Region .","O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Lawrence of Rome","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"The Larry Sanders Show ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Coming on twice as a substitute , he was selected to start in the semi-final loss to Brazil .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG O"
"'' September 7 '' – Little Shop","O O O O O B-PER I-PER"
"It is in Division No. 6 , in the Bay of Exploits .","O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Alexander of Hales , ( died 1245 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Louis Eppolito and Stephen Caracappa","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"''Slavonija '' : Slavonia","O O O B-LOC"
"John Steven Sutherland ( born 11 March 1983 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"K. S. Rangasamy College of Technology","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"St. Mary 's College , Kegalle","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"*Liam references Lucky Charms .","O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Classic Gold Marcher , Wrexham and Chester","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O B-LOC"
"DRS 1 - 101.5 MHz ( 60 kW )","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O"
"Marvin Dunnette , University of Minnesota","B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Get off the Stage","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' Şımarık '' – Tarkan","O B-ORG O O B-PER"
"GMA Network was also reportedly planning to bid but backed out ; it however denied that they offered a bid .","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"' '' Slobodan Živojinović '' ' 7–6 6–3 6–4","O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"K. Stade Leuven ( 1903—2002 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Patrick Ryan ( Irish priest )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Image : V02p108001 Esnoga , Amsterdam , Netherlands","O O O B-ORG O B-LOC O B-LOC"
"'' Graphium endochus '' ( Boisduval , 1836 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Circuit rider ( Technology )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Tachibana no Naramaro","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Rajiv Gandhi International Cricket Stadium","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"- Alanya in Turkey","O B-LOC O B-LOC"
"He was the manager of Árabe Unido in Panama .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O"
"Central , Tennessee ( CDP )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"*20px Indiana State Road 18","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"It is known from Iran and Turkmenistan ( Kopet Dag ) .","O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O O"
"1–0 Ewerthon ( 28 )","O B-PER O O O"
"2014 Women 's Futsal World Tournament","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Guatemalan pygmy owl","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"LAC+USC Medical Center","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Marion Township , Hardin County , Ohio","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' Maurie Keane '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Northern rough-winged swallow","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Caroline Hedwall ( T12 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Winnie the Pooh ( franchise )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Aubrey J. O'Brien","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Including the work of artists such as : Edward Burne-Jones , Ford Madox Brown , John Everett Millais , Dante Gabriel Rossetti , William Holman Hunt , Arthur Hughes , Frederick Sandys , Simeon Solomon .","O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O"
"Weverton , Maryland","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Cleinias of Tarentum","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"The eastward pressure to expand was also created by the inability to move westward , inhibited by the formidable presence of the enormous Flushing Chinatown ( 法拉盛華埠 ) centered on Main Street .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"Arnold Schwarzenegger , Linda Hamilton , Robert Patrick , Edward Furlong","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"List of national libraries","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Frederick Banbury , 1st Baron Banbury of Southam","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"`` Who Loves You ? ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"''Oberst '' Kurt Freiherr von Liebenstein , 21 December 1942 – 1 January 1943 ( acting leader )","O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"** Southern Maryland Blue Crabs","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Casey Janssen ( 6 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"List of famous Puerto Ricans","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"`` Simply Meant to Be '' ( with Jennifer Warnes )","O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"'' Rhodophthitus tricoloraria '' ( Mabille , 1890 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Leo II of Galicia","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"William Morrow and Company","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Wusi Road Subdistrict ( )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O"
"Jane Levy , Dylan Minnette , Stephen Lang","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"It is found in Costa Rica .","O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"In 1841 the population of Norbury and Roston was 510 , in 1895 there were 414 inhabitants .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O"
"''Written by William Barton ''","O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Lantenay ( 01206 )","B-LOC O O O"
"John Reeves ( judge )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"La Clotte ( 17113 )","B-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"Edwin S. Johnson ( D )","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Funahashi Seiichi ( December 25 , 1904 – January 13 , 1976 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O O O"
"It is known from Chile .","O O O O B-LOC O"
"AFL]] ( Australian rules )","O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"Among many artists who recorded this song were Al Jolson and Billy Murray .","O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O"
"** '' Duchy of Aquitaine '' ' – William V ( 995–1030 )","O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"' '' West African lion '' ' ( ''P .","O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O O"
"'' The Room '' ( Chris Waters , Tom Shapiro ) – 3:40","O O O O O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Munsee-Delaware Nation Indian Reserve No. 1 , part of the above","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O O"
"It lies north-west of Kowalewo Pomorskie , north-west of Golub-Dobrzyń , and north-east of Toruń .","O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O O O B-LOC O O O O B-LOC O"
"Bahawalpur Zoo , Bahawalpur , Punjab","B-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O B-ORG"
"Friedrich Gilly ( 1772–1800 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"**** Longtail stingray ( ''D .","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"`` The Woman Comes and Goes '' ( Daryl Hall ) 3:49","O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"List of Orchidaceae genera","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Clarkston railway station","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Rimyongsu Sports Club ( Sariwon )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O"
"Len Braund ( 1901–1907 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Martin Luther King , Jr .","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Verner Thomé ( 1878–1953 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"1944 Presentation Brothers College","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Jörgen Olsson , Sweden","B-PER I-PER O B-LOC"
"''Also see : Hot 100 No. 1 Hits of 1979 ''","O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"He died on March 19 , 1979 in Oakland , California .","O O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"'' Too Many Hands '' ( Randy Meisner , Don Felder ) – 4:43","O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Masonic Temple Building ( Maywood , Illinois )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Shake ( company )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"He ultimately returned to the Boston Globe '' , where he had been working immediately before the ''Tribune '' had hired him .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"'' Psolos fuligo fuligo '' — '' 'Coon '' '","O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Sid Wilson ( 0 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Jan Niklas , Désirée Nosbusch","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"** Trail of Tears , 1830–1838","O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O"
"United States Department of Labor","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Jared Dudley , Emeka Okafor , Jason Richardson ( 9 )","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"The first 3 songs as PopCrush 97.1 were Pitbull / Christina Aguilera 's Feel This Moment '' , Justin Timberlake 's Mirrors '' , and Rihanna 's Umbrella '' .","O O O O O O O O B-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER I-PER O B-ORG O O O B-PER O B-ORG O O"
"Tomáš Šmíd '' ( Third Round )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Chip Robinson ( 1986 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"** ' '' Nanhai '' ' – Liu Yin , King of Nanhai ( 907–911 )","O O O B-ORG O O O B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Siege of Naples ( 542–43 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Clarence Tommerson , NFL player","B-PER I-PER O B-ORG O"
"Naco-Mammoth Kill Site","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' Angiosperms '' '","O O B-ORG O O"
"Magnificent snake eel","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Francisco Menéndez Márquez","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Beecher , Michigan – $ 13,484","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"After a large and well attended funeral , he was interred in Green Lawn Cemetery .","O O O O O O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"List of Indonesian birds : non-passerines","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Stade du 28 Septembre , Conakry","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC"
"' '' Gujranwala '' '","O O B-LOC O O"
"Musa Haji Ismail Galal","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"The song is included in the album Yanni Voces '' .","O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"K. M. Seethi","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"East Chicago , Indiana","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Somerset ( town ) , Wisconsin","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' Mika Häkkinen '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"WTUA St. Stephen , South Carolina","B-ORG B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' Kolkata '' '","O O B-LOC O O"
"Taebong has been overthrown , and Goryeo established in the Korean peninsula , when Wang Kon ascends the throne at Cheorwon .","B-ORG O O O O O B-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-LOC O"
"Sergey Shoygu ( 2012 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Tatem Elementary School , Collingswood , NJ","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Flick of the Switch ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"O. L. Owen ( 1898 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"1911 Yeon Building , Portland , Oregon","O B-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"`` O Come All Ye Faithful ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Conejo Valley Unified School District","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Dick 's Sporting Goods ( 80,000 ft² )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"'' Acianthera rostellata '' ( Barb.Rodr .","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"Calhoun City , Mississippi","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Rockhead ( fish )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Cedar Lawn Cemetery , Paterson , New Jersey","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' CONCACAF Champions ' Cup : ' ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"It was described by Breuning in 1939 .","O O O O B-PER O O O"
"Pontianak ( folklore )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Myrtle Beach , United States","B-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC"
"Tremoschna : Třemošná B,60","O O B-LOC O"
"How to Save a Life ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Parken , Copenhagen ( H )","B-ORG O B-LOC O O O"
"Tenerife , Canary Islands , Spain","B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC"
"Sui Wenjing / Han Cong","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Now under control of 482nd Fighter Wing ( Air Force Reserve Command ) and Detachment 1 , 125th Fighter Wing ( Florida Air National Guard )","O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"אֶת חֶבְרוֹן וְאֶת מִגְרָשֶׁהָ Hebron and its periphery","O O O O B-LOC O O O"
"Voznesensk ( Вознесенський район )","B-LOC O O O O"
"Chimneys of Poolbeg Generating Station","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"This Hour Has 22 Minutes '' cast","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"' '' Lucas Arnold Ker '' ' ' '' Sebastián Prieto '' '","O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Bernhard Warkentin Homestead","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"She currently lives in Los Angeles , California .","O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O"
"Same applied to Polish Americans .","O O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"It was discovered in Oxyrhynchus .","O O O O B-LOC O"
"Princess Clémentine of Belgium","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Andrex ( actor )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Martin Sheen - The West Wing ''","B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"`` U Got It Bad ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"' '' Ruanda-Urundi '' '","O O B-LOC O O"
"Bright Size Life '' – Pat Metheny","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER I-PER"
"Vulcana ( 1875–1946 )","B-PER O O O"
"Society of the Friends of Truth","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Indian flying frog","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Knightville Dam – Westfield River","B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC"
"Aborigines ' Protection Society","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Memphrémagog Regional County Municipality","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' CBS '' '","O O B-ORG O O"
"*1951 - 1980 Sir William Rede Hawthorne","O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Herbert Brownell , Jr .","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"George Caspar Adams ( 1863–1900 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Franz von Papen","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Lee Trevino won the most tournaments , six .","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O"
"East Brunswick , New Jersey .","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Recorded by Fats Waller .","O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Previously , he was head coach at Alcorn State University and an assistant coach at Tulane , Delta State , LSU , Florida , Marshall , Southern Miss , Ole Miss , Michigan , and Memphis .","O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O B-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG O B-ORG O B-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG O O B-LOC O"
"Five years later , in 1939 , Edern was abolished and incorporated into Nefyn .","O O O O O O O B-LOC O O O O O B-LOC O"
"' '' Second : ' '' Kaho Onodera","O O O O O O B-PER I-PER"
"Leopold , Grand Duke of Baden","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Oriole Park at Camden Yards in Baltimore , Maryland , United States","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC"
"Massachusetts Route 3A","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Fulvio Ballabio ( 1988 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Meigs Township , Muskingum County , Ohio","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"He was born in Glasgow , Scotland .","O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC O"
"Gmina Tarnów Opolski","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Hernán Cortés was his relative , whom he accompanied to Mexico ( New Spain ) in 1526 .","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"File : Tiananmen ( 天安门 )","O O B-ORG O O O"
"Episode : `` It 's My Party and I 'll Lie if I Want To ''","O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"He is a son of Alan Lennox-Boyd , 1st Viscount Boyd of Merton .","O O O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O"
"He died on August 25 , 1992 in Boca Raton , Florida .","O O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"'' Nothin ' But Trouble '' ( 1988 )","O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"Lynn Township , McLeod County , Minnesota","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"He resides in Monmouth Junction , New Jersey .","O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"FM Radio Gods","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' Aztec Empire '' ' – Tenoch , Great Speaker ( 1325–1376 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O B-PER O B-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"J. R. R. Tolkien","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"' '' Speed Up '' '","O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"*36th on 10 November 2005 , Calgary CAN","O O O O O O B-LOC B-LOC"
"He graduated in 1970 with a Doctor of veterinary medicine degree from the Ontario Veterinary College , University of Guelph in nearby Guelph , Ontario .","O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-LOC O B-LOC O"
"Paul Tang ( 2007 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Melissa Hayden ( 1945–1947 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Waveguide ( optics )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Las Cruces , New Mexico","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Radu Albot / Artem Sitak , 6–4 , 7–6 ( 7–3 )","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O"
"`` by Arthur Byron Cover","O O B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"'' Aletia infrargyrea ''","O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"The Dirty Dozen Brass Band","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Márcio Rogério de Andrade","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Marshal ( Japan )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Cephissus ( Athenian plain )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Francis Wayland Parker","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"'' Valsa ceratosperma ''","O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"St Ann 's College","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"`` I Promise to Wait My Love ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"National Nursing Week ( United States )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"The Outdoor Room","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Hell : The Sequel ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"He was educated at the Community High School , Tehran and then Carlisle Technical College .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"In 1960 , he joined the U.S. Army , being stationed in Germany for three years .","O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-LOC O O O O"
"Beijing No.8 High School","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Ashdot Ya'akov Meuhad ( 1953 ) , from Ashdot Ya'akov ( 1924 , 1933 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O"
"Lacs de Conzieu","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Monmouth , Illinois – $ 15,839","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"Eastern Anatolia Region","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"He died in July of 1969 in Williamsport , Pennsylvania .","O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"''Review : Something Better to Come '' at Slant Magazine","O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG"
"Returning to Norfolk , Virginia , 1 April 1946 , ''Calamares '' was decommissioned at Baltimore , Maryland , 25 April 1946 , and returned to the War Shipping Administration .","O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Platon ( Kulbusch )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Southampton F.C .","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Chuuk flying fox","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"John Holles , 2nd Earl of Clare","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"The Churches Conservation Trust now cares for the building .","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O"
"They originate from South Asia , Europe , Middle East , and East Africa .","O O O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"Growing Up ( The T.G.I.S. Primetime )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Following its sale by the New Zealand Railways Corporation in the 1990s , the building was turned into student accommodation by Auckland University and since 2008 has been occupied by private apartments .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O"
"' '' With Chet Baker '' '","O O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Çıraqlı , Lachin","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Sağkaya , Ceyhan","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"He is from Andhra Pradesh in South India .","O O O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"53d Wing ( 53 WG )","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"Oda Station ( Shimane ) ( 小田駅 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Tales from Turnpike House ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Aboudeïa – Salamat Region","B-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC"
"Gibaeksan ( South Gyeongsang )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Rufus Choate ( W-MA )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"' '' Tony Albright '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Live - `` Run to the Water ''","B-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Kunio Maekawa , architect","B-PER I-PER O O"
"'' Kingdom of Scotland '' ' – William the Lion ( 1165–1214 )","O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"2008 : Janusz Morgenstern","O O B-PER I-PER"
"'' Platanthera bifolia ''","O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"He spent much of his career with Swindon Town , for whom he played in the Premier League .","O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"The Eastwood Westminster constituency was created in 1983 , and the Eastwood Holyrood constituency , with the same boundaries , in 1999 .","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O"
"UEFA Women 's Euro 2013","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Toulouse '' '","O B-LOC O O"
"Rupert Hamer , LL.M. , MLC","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Ka-Zar '' vol .","B-PER O O O"
"Masters of Darts ( 1 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Time Stays , We Go ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Listed buildings in Crawley","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Michel-Ange Duquesne de Menneville ( 1752–1755 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Poříčí nad Sázavou","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Celaenorrhinus homeyeri '' ( Plötz , 1880 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"J. J. Johnson and Kai Winding","B-PER B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Francisco del Rosario Sánchez , Juan Pablo Duarte and Matías Ramón Mella","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Rupert Young as Sir William Herbert , Lord Pembroke","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Black-bellied plover , ''Pluvialis squatarola ''","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"He is a goalkeeper for Lech Poznań .","O O O B-PER O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"Johannes V. Jensen","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Sean Paul Lockhart","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Montreal West , Quebec","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Văn Lãng District","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"67 competitors were selected by the DLV .","O O O O O O B-ORG O"
"Kalbar , Queensland","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Bobby 's Burger Palace","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Beulah Bondi ( 1888–1981 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Pelican Rapids , Minnesota – $ 13,699","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"This was published by the American Mathematical Society as ISSN 0038-5573 .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"Trilofo , Arcadia","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Melissa , Texas","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"''The Times '' ( Chicago ) , went defunct in 2005","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O"
"Laurence Helsby , Baron Helsby","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Ronaldinho Gaucho 's Team","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Rüppell 's robin-chat","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Thomas 's pine vole","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Tennessee in the Civil War","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Minarete Brass '' ( 2010 )","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"*2008 – `` All Summer Long '' – Kid Rock","O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER I-PER"
"Hamdan bin Mubarak Al Nahyan","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"It 's No Good","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"North Fork Flathead - Canada , United States","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC"
"DCLXVI : To Ride Shoot Straight and Speak the Truth ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"McCoy '' ( 1975-1976 )","B-ORG O O O O"
"The Price Is Right ( Philippine game show ) ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"*** '' Northern March '' ' – Lothair ( 983–1003 )","O O B-LOC I-LOC O O O B-PER O O O"
"' '' Kentucky '' '","O O B-LOC O O"
"He claimed to be son of Khalilullah II .","O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"'' Dialectica imperialella '' ( Zeller , 1847 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Royal Australian Corps of Transport - The Princess Royal","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Johor Bahru City Square","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"It is known from Kenya and Uganda .","O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC O"
"*9378 - Apamea burgessi ''","O O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"Shooting guard / Small forward","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Mount Marty College ( Yankton , South Dakota )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Three 's a Crowd","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"' '' Persiaran APEC '' '","O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"'' Theretra jugurtha '' ( Boisduval , 1875 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Harvard Business School Press ( 2013 ) Managing Up : Expert Solutions to Everyday Challenges","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O"
"Marysville , Pennsylvania","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"St. Mary 's Church , South Stoneham","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"He was a son of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart .","O O O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O"
"He hailed from Søgne .","O O O B-LOC O"
"Njego Pesa ( 1983–87 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"' '' Marco Melandri '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Sun Quan : Nabatame Hitomi","B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG"
"David Clarke ( Paralympic footballer )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Comanche , Oklahoma","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Bova , Calabria","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Lamb 's Conduit Field","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Doug McClure , Keith Barron","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Howard W. Hunter , Boyd K. Packer , Marvin J. Ashton , L. Tom Perry , David B. Haight , James E. Faust , Neal A. Maxwell , Russell M. Nelson , Dallin H. Oaks , M. Russell Ballard , Joseph B. Wirthlin , Richard G. Scott","B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"`` I 'll Walk ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Silver Slipper , Las Vegas , Nevada","B-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Top Chef : Just Desserts ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"`` Wake Up Brother ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Pemba green pigeon","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"The ' '' 1994 Big Ten Conference Baseball Tournament '' ' was held at C. O. Brown Stadium in Battle Creek , Michigan from May 15 through 19 .","O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"' '' Robert B. Mautz '' '","O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O"
"`` Carnival '' – Natalie Merchant","O B-ORG O O B-PER I-PER"
"Sharif Fati Ali Al Mishad","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Prince Talal bin Muhammad","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"2000 - Servants of Darkness ''","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Anne McLellan ( 1994-1997 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"The demand is $ .","O O O B-ORG O"
"Thomas Morgan ( MP died 1565 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"' '' Giancarlo Fisichella '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"The People 's Petition","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"He was Mayor of Exeter July 1414 to October 1415 .","O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"Brays Oaks , Houston","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"He became a journalist for The Nashville American '' , serving as a correspondent from 1885 to 1892 .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O"
"Evans Bay is nearby .","B-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"** Basilica of San Isidoro , León , Spain consecrated .","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O"
"Sir Gilbert Heathcote , 3rd Baronet ( died 1785 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Lee Maye , LF ( 1965-1966 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"' '' Venue : ' '' Daegu Civic Stadium , Daegu","O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC"
"Policarpo Cacherano d'Osasco","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Parliamentary elections on 22 September 2002 : 44.1 % of the primary vote","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O"
"'' Elachista quadripunctella '' ( Hübner , 1825 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"It is found in Cameroon and São Tomé and Príncipe .","O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Rupert Keegan took the B.A.R.C .","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Miranda Cosgrove ( 1993- )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"' '' Mark Knowles '' ' / ' '' Daniel Nestor '' ' defeated Roger Federer / Max Mirnyi 6–4 , 6–4","O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O B-PER I-PER O O O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Uluçınar , İmamoğlu","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"José Luis de Arrese","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"''65 Damien Woody G ( IR ) 7px","O B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Joppatowne , Maryland","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Jackie Evancho '' ' ( born 2000 )","O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"NALSAR University of Law , Hyderabad","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC"
"Toronto , Ontario - CITY","B-LOC O B-LOC O B-ORG"
"`` Livin ' on Borrowed Time ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"José Luis Reséndez","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Broadcaster RAI chose the song and performer internally .","O B-ORG O O O O O O O"
"Mystery Science Theater 3000 ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"J. J. Kelso","B-PER B-PER I-PER"
"Byzantium under the Macedonians","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Johan Caspar von Cicignon","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"North Vacherie , Louisiana","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"1 : `` No News '' , `` Come Cryin ' to Me '' , `` Amazed '' , `` Smile '' , `` What About Now '' , `` Tell Her '' , `` I 'm Already There '' , `` My Front Porch Looking In '' , and `` Mr. Mom '' .","O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O B-ORG O O O B-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Shakira – `` Ojos Así ''","B-PER O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"North Woodbridge , California","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Simone Terenzani ( 0,0,1,0,0,1,1,0 ) - 38 .","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"'' Catocala puerpera '' ( Giorna , 1791 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"List of counties in Missouri","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"The Threshold of a Persona","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' Grapholita funebrana '' Treitschke , 1835","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"Rube Ellis ( 1911 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"*1986 : Herbert W. Franke , ''Endzeit ''","O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Miranda de Azán","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' Bukit Kepong '' '","O O B-LOC I-LOC O O"
"Volcanoes National Park , Rwanda","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC"
"Terry George ( entrepreneur )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Based in Lille and Versailles .","O O B-LOC O B-LOC O"
"The John Tracy Clinic , named after her son , was the result .","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O"
"*The Bennington Battle Monument in Bennington , Vermont , 1889 .","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"Westwood College – Dallas , Texas","B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Anabelle Langlois / Patrice Archetto","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Part of the state-owned Main Line of Public Works","O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Madiran Tannat ( 4–12 yrs )","B-ORG B-LOC O O O O"
"Mia Wasikowska as Alice Kingsleigh .","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O"
"Alexandru Popovici ( 2001 Seongnam Ilhwa Chunma )","B-PER I-PER O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"' '' If You Ai n't Got a Weapon ... ''","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"It consists of the Bundesautobahn 3 , the Bundesautobahn 4 and the Bundesautobahn 1 .","O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"There have been five winners to date : Leanne Mitchell , Andrea Begley , Jermain Jackman , Stevie McCrorie and Kevin Simm .","O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG O B-PER I-PER O"
"Francesco Soto de Langa ( 1534–1619 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"' '' 14 Porsche '' ' ''","O O O B-ORG O O O"
"He subsequently worked for ABC affiliate WUTR in Utica , New York , CBS affiliate WTVH in Syracuse , New York , and NBC affiliate WCNC-TV in Charlotte , North Carolina .","O O O O B-ORG O B-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-ORG O B-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O B-ORG O B-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"There were two main branches of the family , one in Dutton and the other in Sutton Weaver .","O O O O O O O O O O O B-LOC O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"'' ' '' After the Love Has Gone '' Earth , Wind & Fire '' '","O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Decius ( 249-251 )","B-PER O O O"
"Seán Óg Ó hAilpín : 3 ( 2003 , 2004 , 2005 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O"
"*Has made several trips to the Middle East , visiting troops in Iraq and Afghanistan , as well as visiting Kyrgyzstan , Afghanistan , Kuwait , Bahrain , Saudi Arabia , the United Arab Emirates and Qatar .","O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC O O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O"
"'' Last Date '' ( Floyd Cramer ) – 2:16","O O O O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Giovanni Battista Buonamente","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Tazmania '' ( 2006 )","B-ORG O O O O"
"' '' Marcello Trotta ' ''","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"2369 Shickshinny , Pennsylvania $ 14,880","O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O"
"Patagonian yellow finch","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' President 's Cup '' '","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"*Mr. Grimby - Richard Dumont","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"'' Tokimeki Memorial : Forever With You ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"*The consisted of Centre , Clearfield , Lycoming , McKean , Northumberland , Potter , and Tioga Counties","O O O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O O B-LOC I-LOC"
"Arnaud Boetsch '' ( Second round ) ''","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"' '' Lornna Soto '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"It premiered on 27 June 2010 on YouTube .","O O O O O O O B-ORG O"
"Wesley Pritchard ( 1996– ) 36","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Damon Stoudamire ( 3,018 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Călineasa River ( Someșul Cald )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Camille Paglia compares the resulting image to William Blake 's `` engravings of solipsistically contorted figures '' .","B-PER I-PER O O O O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O"
"Assemblyman Peter J. Barnes III ( D )","O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"In 1854 he was appointed to a seat on the Legislative Council of Nova Scotia , upon the recommendation of William Young .","O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Mark McGrath ( 2010–2011 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Twickenham Stadium , London , England","B-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O B-LOC"
"File : Southern Italy and Sicily on the 1849 map .","O O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O O O O O"
"Petersburg , Virginia","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"His descendants include Vincenzo Viviani , a disciple and biographer of Galileo Galilei .","O O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"This was continued by his sons Edgar , Alexander I and in particular David I .","O O O O O O B-PER O B-PER I-PER O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"He was Sworn in as a Member of the Queen 's Privy Council for Canada on 4 January 2011 .","O O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"John Henry Crichton , Viscount Crichton","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"She was the youngest-ever female Member of Parliament .","O O O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O"
"The song was recorded at Grouse Lodge , under the supervision of producer Jacknife Lee .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Krapanj , population 170","B-LOC O O O"
"Ronald J. Garan , Jr . Michael E. Fossum","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"San Pedro y San Pablo Asistencia","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' Telamoptilia hemistacta '' ( Meyrick , 1918 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Red knot , ''Calidris canutus '' ( A )","B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O O"
"La Seyne-sur-Mer – 57,553","B-LOC I-LOC O O"
"border ' '' Séamus Harnedy","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"** Western gorilla ( ''G .","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"Lyraka Volume 1 ( 2010 ) ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"' '' Brunei '' '","O O B-LOC O O"
"Hälsingland Rune Inscription 21","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Joe Abercrombie , author ;","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Judge Reinhold , Fred Savage","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Melaleuca delta '' Craven","B-LOC I-LOC O B-PER"
"The Beatles ' influence on popular culture","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"His death was profiled in an episode of Unsolved Mysteries '' .","O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"'' Agrochola lota '' ( Clerck , 1759 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Highest total against : 224 / 7 by Somerset at Taunton , 2015","O O O O O O O O B-ORG O B-LOC O O"
"'' Mordellistena pseudoparvula '' Ermisch , 1956","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"All Saints Cathedral , Halifax","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Beginning of Karoo Ice Age .","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"It is housed in the Musée du Louvre of Paris .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O"
"Lotte Jonathans Paulien van Dooremalen","B-ORG I-ORG B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Serra da Estrela Subregion","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"**09621 Amberg ( Oberpfalz )","O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
": : : B. ''","O O O B-LOC O"
"The Jacksons ( TV series )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Reagan County , Texas","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"E. H. Shepard","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
": Ashleigh Brewer ( 2014– )","O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Nowinki , Wołomin County","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Lyrics : Duncan Fallowell ) – 3:30 / 5:41","O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"*Lifetime Achievement - Arthur M. Schlesinger , Jr .","O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Hans Karl von Diebitsch","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"'' Crombrugghia distans '' ( Zeller , 1847 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Rob Fusari – composer , producer","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"William O'Connor '' ( First round )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Albert Pujols [2] ( 2006 , 2010 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"Mark Jones : ( 1991-1999 , 2006 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"Lugdunum ( modern Lyon )","B-LOC O O B-LOC O"
"Pioneer Square , Seattle","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Joe Shirley , Jr .","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"The family eventually settled in Egypt in February 1944 .","O O O O O B-ORG O O O O"
"'' Pumped Up Kicks '' – Foster the People","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"' '' Tanzania '' ' - Jakaya Kikwete ( 1995-2006 )","O O B-LOC O O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Brian Dillons GAA","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Ridley Scott / Hans Zimmer","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Slavko Marić – Hajduk Beograd ( 2001–2006 ) , Mladost Lučani ( 2006–2008 ) , Borac Čačak ( 2008–2011 ) , Sloboda Užice ( 2011–2012 ) , Radnički Kragujevac ( 2012-2014 ) , ' '' FK Jagodina '' ' ( 2015–present )","B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O"
"It was described by Breuning in 1982 .","O O O O B-PER O O O"
"Shipley , West Yorkshire","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Jefferson Davis ! ! 2 ! !","B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"They wed on 28 April 2007 in their Malibu home .","O O O O O O O O B-LOC O O"
"Native North American Child : An Odyssey ''","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Redlich–Kwong equation of state","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Yu Darvish ( TEX ) :","B-PER I-PER O B-ORG O O"
"'' Samurai 7 ''","O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"Dev ( actor )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Party of Action ( POA )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Princess Adélaïde of Orléans","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Children 's Day Festival","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Hedley , Texas","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Final Fantasy concerts","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Quta Qutani ( Bolivia )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' 20px 99 Villeray '' '","O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"A Few Days with Me ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Crick , Northamptonshire","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"List of Serbian monarchs","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"R. Kelly – `` Satisfy You ''","B-PER I-PER O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"Turkish films of 2010","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' Nemapogon ruricolella '' ( Stainton , 1859 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Latter Day Church of Christ","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"' '' DLCX '' ' - Waste Management , Inc .","O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"the `` Twelve Steps '' at the beginning of Chapter 5 `` How It Works ''","O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"Boundary Ranges , just S of Iskut River","B-LOC I-LOC O O O O B-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Volumes 3 & 4 '' ( 1998 )","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"Cauchy 's theorem ( geometry )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Eaton High School ( grades 9-12 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"Prince Michael of Prussia ( 1940–2014 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Anastasia Martiusheva / Alexei Rogonov","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"C.D. Atlético Junior","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Stick ( unit )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Bridgwater Town , promoted as runners-up in Western League","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC"
"`` The Heart Wo n't Lie '' ( Kim Carnes , Donna Weiss ) - 3:22","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Exeter Cathedral 1929 - 1937","B-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"''Crockett '' was laid down by the Tacoma Boatbuilding Company , Tacoma , Washington , and commissioned 24 June 1967 .","O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O O"
"Morrisania , Bronx","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Governorate General of Brazil ( 1549-1572 / 1578-1607 / 1613-1621 )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O O"
"Football League Two third-place promotion : 2005–06","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O B-ORG"
"International Swimming Federation ( FINA )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Ethnic stereotypes in comics","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Chestnut-capped brush finch","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' Spain '' '","O O B-LOC O O"
"09:00 PM ( VIA : Alagankulam )","O O O O O B-LOC O"
"Air Command and Staff College , Seminar Program","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"'' Eilema depressa '' ( Esper , 1787 )","O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O"
"North Carolina General Assembly of 2003–04","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' Robopit '' - Kokopeli Digital Studios / Altron","O B-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG"
"Dominic Mafham as Robin Douglas-Home","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"She was purposely sunk near Les Bergeronnes , Quebec in November 1960 .","O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"Vasil Levski National Military University , Veliko Tarnovo","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC"
"Smokey Robinson handled much of the production .","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"Member of Finnish Academy of Sciences , 2002–","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Michael Jackson – `` Earth Song ''","B-PER I-PER O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"National Union of Students ( Canada ) ( disbanded )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Patti McLeod276 ( 37.8 % )","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"The resulting album , Last Fair Deal Gone Down '' was released in May 2001 .","O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O"
"43 - Nutpimon Natthayalak , ( Krabi )","O O B-PER I-PER O O B-LOC O"
"'' Papilio alexanor '' Esper , 1800","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"Thief River Falls , Minnesota","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Persona 2 : Innocent Sin","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Rhododendron subg. Rhododendron","B-LOC I-LOC B-LOC"
"Aleksander Barkov , Jr .","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"`` Express Yourself '' , Madonna ( 1989 )","O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER O O O"
"Tony Parker ( 24 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Pierre Du Moulin","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Thalhimers ( Richmond )","B-ORG O B-LOC O"
"Phil Gramm ( R-TX )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"John Isner 7–6 ( 4 ) , 5–7 ( 5 ) , 7–5 , 6–4","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"'' Eupithecia refertissima ''","O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"He is part of the Czech Republic men 's national volleyball team .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"800BC ( in The Odyssey '' )","O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Dakaongo ( 1 245 inhabitants )","B-LOC O O O O O"
"Center Township , Atchison County , Kansas","B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' Turkish Super Cup '' ' ''","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Metadata Object Description Schema","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Events from the year ' '' 1866 in Scotland '' ' .","O O O O O O O O B-LOC O O O"
"It lies approximately south-east of Sicienko and north-west of Bydgoszcz .","O O O O O B-LOC O O O B-LOC O"
"Ted Freyer ( 52 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Joe Barry Carroll , Golden State Warriors","B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"He joined Ayr United in August 1999 , and remained with them until August 2000 .","O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"' '' Perth Thunder '' '","O O B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Maria Adams ( disambiguation )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Johann Ludwig Krebs","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Constantine Dragaš ( Dragaš )","B-PER I-PER O B-LOC O"
"Ami Koshimizu and Mamiko Noto","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Gérald V d'Armagnac","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Banyan ( clothing )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"He migrated to Mexico City in 1986 .","O O O B-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"Basilica della Santa Casa","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Full Circle '' ( 2004 )","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"'' Col des Ares ''","O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Barry Mackay '' ( Quarterfinalist ) ''","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O"
"Michael Bolton covered the song on his 1992 album Timeless : The Classics '' .","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O"
"Christopher Andersen , journalist and author","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Till 2014 , the NMMC was headquartered in an eight storied building in CBD Belapur .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"Represented Indigenous All-Stars ( 2009 )","O B-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Southend United F.C .","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Episodes '' , 2011 ( writer / producer )","B-ORG O O O O O O O O"
"1992 Major League Baseball expansion draft","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Crystal Snow Jenne","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Siliștea River ( Țibrin )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Happy]] '' – Pharrell Williams","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"Premier ( Canada )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Patterson Township , Beaver County , Pennsylvania","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Vinod Khanna , Shabana Azmi","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Benjamin N. Cardozo","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Herbie Hancock ( born 1940 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Jonathan Thomas , 3 .","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Cark and Cartmel railway station","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"*Written by Val Guest and Leslie Thomas","O O B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Anurag Singh , 2012 / 13-2014 / 15","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"National Coalition Party 13.5 %","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Beauvoir De Lisle , 1st Dragoons , commanded both the XIII and XV Corps .","B-PER I-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"Eastwood , Houston","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Jacqueline Novogratz is the founder and CEO of Acumen .","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O"
"`` Sign of the Times '' ( Bryan Ferry song ) , 1978","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Szczecin – 95.7 MHz","B-LOC O O O"
"It is found in Ecuador .","O O O O B-LOC O"
"Billy Vessels ( RB ) :","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Houston , Tennessee","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Lake of Banyoles and S'Agaró","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-ORG"
"Bugs Bunny , Yosemite Sam","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"Buxton & Leek College","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"** Maués marmoset , ''Mico mauesi ''","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"'' The World at Large '' – 4:32","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"*Assemblyman Bob Andrzejczak ( D ) , and","O B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Seidou Njimoluh Njoya","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"It is headquartered in Raleigh .","O O O O B-LOC O"
"May 10 – Shel Silverstein , 68 , children 's poet","O O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
": PG 87a-87b : Procopius of Gaza","O O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"State Senate District 39","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Miyazaki Athletic Stadium","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
": '' Atomic Dog '' by George Clinton","O O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER I-PER"
"They currently reside in Lexington , Massachusetts .","O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"1:46.7 – Edward Burns","O O B-PER I-PER"
"C & D Canal Museum","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Alexander Grant ( Massachusetts politician ) ( 1853– ?","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"`` Stupid Shit '' – Girlicious","O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG"
"Emerson Aparecido Vivas Vergílio","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"South Los Angeles","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Burmese–Siamese War ( 1759–60 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Dance4life event 2006 .","B-ORG O O O"
"'' 'Megahertz '' ' from Mighty Med ''","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"' '' The Green Monkey '' '","O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O"
"`` Elégie '' ( Jules Massenet )","O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"He came to Rossland , British Columbia in 1898 .","O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"All degrees ( whether traditional on-campus , or distance ) are recognized by the New England Association of Schools and Colleges and the State of Connecticut ; .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"' '' Ifni '' '","O O B-LOC O O"
"Oslo – Ullevaal Stadion ( 25,572 )","B-LOC O B-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Tommy Aaron ( 1 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"' '' Sam Lowes '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"The Malwa Subah existed from 1568 to 1743 .","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"San Cristóbal de La Laguna , España","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"The song contains samples from `` Try Again '' by Aaliyah , `` Breathe and Stop '' by Q-Tip , and `` N.T .","O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER O O O O O"
"Holy Trinity Church , Blythburgh","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' Pick-Up '' ( 1933 ) with Sylvia Sidney","O B-ORG O O O O O B-PER I-PER"
": Hans N. Andersen ( 11 )","O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Kevin Johnson ( 9 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"' '' Riccardo Patrese '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"The founder Mustafa Kemal Atatürk died .","O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O"
"He was TV-host for Parlamentet in 2011 .","O O O O B-ORG O O O"
"' '' James Auckland '' ' ' '' Travis Rettenmaier '' '7–5 , 6–7 ( 6 ) , [10–4]","O O B-PER I-PER O O O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O"
"' '' 7th US Army HQ , Heidelberg '' ' , FRG","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O O O O"
"He was born in Upton , Massachusetts and died in Worcester , Massachusetts .","O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Jesús Rubio Martín","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Amanda Magarian / Jered Guzman","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER"
"He is buried in Père Lachaise Cemetery .","O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Sivaji Ganesan , Sripriya , V.K. Ramasamy","B-PER I-PER O B-PER O B-ORG I-ORG"
"Both his parents were members of the Plymouth Brethren .","O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Bourke-White , Margaret .","B-PER I-PER I-PER O"
"Marquis de Condorcet","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"*12 August 1681 : Charles Bertie","O O O O B-PER I-PER"
"Chita Rivera played the role of `` The Leader '' .","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O"
"' '' Cate Blanchett '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Free Software Foundation Europe","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Way of the Blade '' ( 2006 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"**Monarch – Emperor Go-Daigo ( 1318–1339 )","O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Bhagwan Mahaveer Sanctuary and Mollem National Park","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"NBA Rookie of the Year : 2007","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"A modern Twist ( ride ) .","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"1–1 Rodrigo Taddei ( 54 )","O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Double Bayou , Texas","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"The album was a commercial success and sold almost eight million copies , according to Billboard '' .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG O O"
"Jaipur ( Palace of the Winds )","B-LOC O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Norte Region , Portugal","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Digitised copy from Internet Archive .","O O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"US Amateur – Bobby Jones","B-ORG I-ORG O B-PER I-PER"
"Port of Spain , Trinidad and Tobago","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"( 82.07 ) ' '' Colin Osborne '' '","O O O O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"' '' Women 's 10,000 metres '' '","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"New Forest Wildlife Park - Hampshire","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC"
"— Arranging lessons from Willie Maiden","O O O O B-PER I-PER"
"Henry I of Werle","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Venice Canal Historic District","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Richard Hanson Weightman","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"All tracks written by Ray Davies","O O O O B-PER I-PER"
"`` California Gurls '' - Katy Perry","O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER I-PER"
"Brian O'Driscoll ( capt .","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Victory shared with Eugen Bönsch","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"19 , , Stockholm , Cirkus","O O O B-LOC O B-ORG"
"Waverly School District ( disambiguation )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"It is found in Europe .","O O O O B-LOC O"
"Lone Tree , Iowa","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Metanarsia guberlica '' Nupponen , 2010","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"Dwyane Wade ( 39 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"2004 : Real Gone Tour ''","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Replaced by Robbie Groff .","O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Interstate 88 ( Illinois )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Isle of Man Railway stations","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"632 , Air Force Office of Special Investigations","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"`` Gin and Juice ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"There is some intimation that Father Set may be one of the Great Old Ones that H. P. Lovecraft created .","O O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O"
"' '' Dušan Lajović '' ' 7–6 ( 7–5 ) , 7–6 ( 7–5 )","O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O O O"
"before 1870 and the Third Republic or","O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O"
"Owl Eyes – `` Pumped Up Kicks '' ( Foster the People )","B-PER I-PER O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"K ( Eighth Avenue Local )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"' '' WCAU-TV '' '","O O B-ORG O O"
"List of B-52 Units of the United States Air Force","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"** High Explosive ( HE )","O B-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"His son , John V , cosied up to Guaimar IV of Salerno and eventually did homage to him .","O O O B-PER I-PER O O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O O O"
"( ** Represents NFL Combine )","O O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"Francisco Clavet Marcelo Ríos Takao Suzuki Sjeng Schalken","B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER"
"Head coach : Todor Veselinović","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"Council of Churches of Malaysia","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' The Partridge Family ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"File : J150W-Ayers.jpg |Sir Henry Ayers","O O O O B-PER I-PER"
"Pedro Téllez-Girón , 1st Duke of Osuna","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"BP Ford Abu Dhabi World Rally Team","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Common ringed plover , ''Charadrius hiaticula ''","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"Villefranche near Nice .","B-LOC O B-LOC O"
"`` Love Needs No Disguise ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Mang Thít District","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"( See article : Entropy ( statistical views ) ) .","O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Lancelot Strong , the Shield '' 1-2 ( 1983 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"''Look Out , Houndour !","O O O B-ORG O"
"Midnight at Minton 's '' ( 1941 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"Legal systems of the world","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"This was the first production that Charlie Chaplin came to .","O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Milt Pappas , 2012","B-PER I-PER O O"
"He died in Romillé .","O O O B-LOC O"
"The ports of Cádiz , La Spezia , Naples and Toulon were visited .","O O O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O O O"
"Geneva II Conference on Syria","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Stoke Bridge , Ipswich","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' Teniorhinus niger '' ( Druce , 1910 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Aloha Bowl : 22 Michigan State 33 , 23 13","B-ORG I-ORG O O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"'' Scoparia niphospora '' ( Meyrick , 1884 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"*1973 ''North Face '' , Wetterhorn Peak , San Juan Mountains , Colorado .","O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O"
"Pic du Midi de Bigorre , France ( ''ETs '' )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O O O O"
"Arnold , Nebraska – $ 18,574","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"West Melbourne , Victoria","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"'' Mythimna impura '' ( Hübner , 1808 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O"
"Nicolaus Olahus ( 1543 - 1548 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Roy Stewart as Nosha ( uncredited )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Palau Municipal d'Esports de Badalona","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Glenwood ( vast majority )","B-LOC O O O O"
"Imperial College Business School","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"53 feet ( 16 m ) - Squaw Island Light , Michigan","O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC"
"José Luís Ábalos Meco","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"U.S. Route 211","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"She was reportedly set against moving from St Albans , Hertfordshire to York , North Yorkshire , resulting in her husband turning down the offer .","O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O O O O O"
"List of works by Auguste Carli","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"In September 2011 , he signed a one-year contract with PAOK in Greece .","O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG O B-LOC O"
"Six Celan Songs • The Ballad of Kastriot Rexhepi","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"E.A. Diddle Arena , Bowling Green , Kentucky","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"1968–69 Honduran Liga Nacional","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Drums and Guns","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Pat Garrity , George McCloud ( 15 )","B-PER I-PER O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"He started by beating Iván Navarro in straight sets and eventually lost to 12th ranked David Ferrer .","O O O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Aspropotamos , Trikala","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"In 1606 and 1607 the Plymouth Company sent ships into the area to colonize , but the settlers of the Popham Colony and those who settled along the Kennebec River returned to England in 1608 .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O O B-LOC O O O"
"' '' King Edward Point '' '","O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O"
"The Power Team ( TV series )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Barbara Schett Amanda Coetzer Jana Novotná Lindsay Davenport","B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER"
"Bad Schwartau , Schleswig-Holstein","B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC"
"** '' Kingdom of Pamplona '' ' - García Sánchez II ( 994–1004 )","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Dwight Howard ( 12 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"' '' Chris Short '' ' ( 6–7 )","O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"' '' Olli Tuominen '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Lalit Mohan Sharma , former Chief Justice of India","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"A Dramatic Turn of Events '' ( 2011 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"''Lawe '' left the Gulf of Tonkin on 14 May .","O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"North Frontenac , Ontario","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Red Raw & Sore ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"** Aljunied GRC , Ang Mo Kio GRC , Cheng San GRC , Hong Kah GRC were increased from four -member GRCs to five-member GRCs .","O B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O O"
"Ian Woosnam ( 2 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Roman Rudenko ( 1907–1981 )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"It is found in Bolivia and Peru .","O O O O B-LOC O B-LOC O"
"Colegio de la Preciosa Sangre de Pichilemu","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"'' 'QB '' ' - AJ McCarron , Alabama ( ' '' AFCA '' ' , ' '' WCFF '' ' )","O O O O O B-PER I-PER O B-LOC O O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"Tebeau , Charlton W .","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O"
"Okolona , Arkansas – $ 14,318","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"Hip Hop and the World We Live In '' ( 2002 )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O O"
"' '' Scott Pruett '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Berliner FC Dynamo ( 6 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Dar Gol-e Seyyed Hasan","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Captain Miša 's Mansion","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"In 2001 he was elected the Rector of the University of Dundee .","O O O O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O"
"Deputy-mayor of Massy , Essonne , 1983–1995 .","O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"Galway , Ireland ( since 1987 )","B-LOC O B-LOC O O O O"
"Galapagos snake eel","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"The album 's lead single , titled `` Bounce with Me '' was released on August 8 , 2000 .","O O O O B-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O O O O"
"*** Mountain Standard Time ( UTC-07 ) , Mountain Daylight Time ( UTC-06 )","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG O"
"Philip Glass ( 1937- )","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"White Mountain National Forest","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Vilar do Paraíso","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Stapleton Cotton , 1st Viscount Combermere","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Before 1945 the area was part of Germany .","O O O O O O O B-LOC O"
"' '' John Eckstein '' '","O O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Zaal'Koris is voiced by Martin Jarvis .","O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Peter Sandhu5,446 ( 39.58 % )","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"`` Ca n't Get You Out of My Head '' by Kylie Minogue","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O B-PER I-PER"
"Celtic Park , Glasgow ( 60,832 )","B-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O O O"
"Giovanni Battista Riccioli","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"In October 1890 , uncertain of his destination , he boarded the Union Pacific Railroad in Omaha .","O O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC O"
"Joe Perry ( June 6 , 1992 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"She has received honorary degrees from the University of Utah , Weber State University , Salt Lake Community College , and the College of Eastern Utah .","O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Davao City - General Santos City","B-LOC I-LOC O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Larissos ( near Araxos )","B-LOC O O B-LOC O"
"She also used some handcrafted techniques which she displayed at the 1935 Brussels International Exhibition .","O O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"François Le Lionnais ( October 3 , 1901 – March 13 , 1984 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O O O"
"William Eggleston ( born 1939 ) , photographer","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"Bannered routes of U.S. Route 6","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Punta del Este / Montevideo","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC"
"'' Canal des houillères de la Sarre '' in Gondrexange","O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O B-LOC"
"CONCACAF U-17 Championship","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Walter B. Woodbury","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"W , New Hampshire Jr. Monarchs ( EJHL ) 2-1","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"Scott Sharp Johannes van Overbeek","B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Roadway flooding along U.S. Route 130 was reported in Collingswood .","O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O B-LOC O"
"The first recipient was his replacement , George Hainsworth .","O O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Croy , Highland and Dalcross , Highland","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Communist Party of Nepal ( UML )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Defending titlist is Kaisa Mäkäräinen of Finland .","O O O B-PER I-PER O B-LOC O"
"' '' Gisselberg '' ' is a Stadtteil of Marburg in Hesse .","O O O O O O O B-ORG O B-LOC O B-LOC O"
"Luis de Morales","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"The main opposition parties of Fine Gael and the Labour Party were also in favour .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O"
"24 Apr – Heinrich Himmler","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"File : Lhasatrainstation Lhasa Railway Station","O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"He appeared in an episode of Gibbsville '' in 1976 .","O O O O O O B-ORG O O O O"
"30 June - Opening of the Prichard Jones Institute at Newborough , Anglesey .","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Medfra , Alaska","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Bermudian Springs High School , York Springs","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC"
"Reichenau , Switzerland","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Juan de Araujo ( 1646–1712 )","B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Outline of the creation–evolution controversy","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"LaGrange , New York","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Ray ( wrestler )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Henry II the Pious","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Natchez , Mississippi","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' Daytime Emmy Awards '' '","O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Maha Sarakham University , Thailand","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC"
"Thunderon is voiced by Alonzo Bodden .","O O O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Hissar ( disambiguation )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"** '' Duchy of Gaeta '' ' - John I , Hypatus of Gaeta ( 906–933 )","O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O O O B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Putties ( a.k.a .","B-ORG O O O"
"Shazia Sikander ( M.F.A .","B-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Colin Allan ( 1973-1976 ) •","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"Joe Presko , P , 1957–1958","B-PER I-PER O O O O"
"' '' Deadmau5 '' '","O O B-PER O O"
"It is found on the Galapagos Islands .","O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O"
"He served as Chief Justice of India from 1943 to 1947 .","O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Nick Slyney , 12 .","B-PER I-PER O O O"
"JGC Corporation ( )","B-ORG I-ORG O O"
"He was named to the second-team Big East along with Tyvon Branch .","O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC O O B-PER I-PER O"
"Two tramcars survive , both in the National Tramway Museum collection .","O O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O"
"Reed Between the Lines ''","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Prince of Lies '' , by James Lowder ( paperback , August 1993 , ISBN 978-1-56076-626-1 ; paperback re-issue , September 2003 , ISBN 978-0-7869-3114-9 )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"Charles I , Duke of Brunswick-Wolfenbüttel","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
": : : A. ''","O O O B-LOC O"
"M. B. W. Tent","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Solicitor General for England and Wales – Harriet Harman – 2001","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-PER I-PER O O"
"Premier of Newfoundland - Clyde Wells","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-PER I-PER"
"Tom Corcoran , author","B-PER I-PER O O"
"** European Astronaut Centre ( ''EAC '' ) of the European Space Agency ;","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"John Parr , producer","B-PER I-PER O O"
"Interchange ( road )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Royal Hospital for Sick Children - University of Glasgow","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"• Donja Nevlja ( 31 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O"
"Sultan of Johor : Sultan Ibrahim Ismail","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Uliana of Tver","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Abbey of Our Lady of Gethsemani","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"• Smoljinac ( 1873 )","O B-LOC O O O"
"National Gallery of Australia","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Deportivo Pereira ( 1 )","B-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"Strikeforce : Feijao vs. Henderson","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"The case is steeply conical and headspaces on the conical case walls .","O O O O O O B-ORG O O O O O O"
"' '' Related '' '","O O B-ORG O O"
"Graeme Le Saux","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Aldeburgh ( UK Parliament constituency )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"*Released as a Mick Jagger solo single in November 1970","O O O B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"There are currently 76 vehicles available to members , with the majority of them located in Kitchener-Waterloo .","O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-ORG O"
"FedEx Express operates Boeing 767-300F and Airbus A300-600","B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG"
"Tracks ( Bruce Springsteen album )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Griffin ( Dan Vado )","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"'' Byzantine Empire '' ' - John V Palaiologos ( 1341–1391 )","O B-LOC I-LOC O O O B-PER I-PER I-PER O O O"
"Indianapolis , Kansas City , Portland , St. Louis and Hartford are tied with three each .","B-ORG O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O B-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC O O O O O O"
"Army of the Potomac","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"** Lars Frederiksen and the Bastards – Lars Frederiksen and the Bastards ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Eileen M. Rehrmann","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Chicago Bulls ( waived on December 16 )","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O O O"
"He was defeated for re-election by Travis Tranel in 2010 .","O O O O O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Elizabeth Charleston , painter","B-PER I-PER O O"
"Ctenopharynx '' ( 3 species )","B-LOC O O O O O"
"`` Dead By X-Mas '' ( 1981 )","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"P. J. Nolan","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
": Marcus Tulio Tanaka","O B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Kubrat , Prince of Panagyurishte .","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER O"
"Charismatic Episcopal Church bishops","B-PER I-PER I-PER I-PER"
"** United States Post Office ( Jackson Heights , Queens )","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"He was a Democrat .","O O O B-ORG O"
"Kyle Farnsworth came on and got the third out , but the damage was done .","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O O O O O O O O"
"Sydney Cricket Ground , Sydney","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O B-LOC"
"Laz River ( Someș )","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Joseph L. Doob","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Wemindji , Quebec","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"Kate Sullivan - anchor / reporter ( 2000–2006 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O O"
"Cap-d'Ail , France ( H )","B-LOC O B-LOC O O O"
"Pine Grove , Amador County , California","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
": Zvolen , Slovakia - 2007","O B-LOC O B-LOC O O"
"Ekaterina Makarova Bruno Soares ( 1 / 3 )","B-PER I-PER B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Ketevan Orbeliani ( according to tradition )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O"
"Papua New Guinea","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"' '' Skindred '' '","O O B-ORG O O"
"Lago di Bilancino","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"; *NSYNC – No Strings Attached ''","O B-ORG O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Calcium channel blocker","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Common whimbrel , ''Numenius phaeopus ''","B-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"Within Gujarat , India ,","O B-LOC O B-LOC O"
"'' Marians Pahars '' ' – Anorthosis Famagusta FC ( 2006–2007 )","O B-PER I-PER O O O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O"
"List of number-one singles in 2004 ( New Zealand )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"Michael Stephens , Chicago Fire","B-PER I-PER O B-ORG I-ORG"
"`` I 'm Addicted ''","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O"
"Valea Urșilor River","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
", performed by Lera Auerbach","O O O B-PER I-PER"
"rect 1782 386 1833 488 Walter Jacobi","O O O O O B-PER I-PER"
"West Ukrainian People 's Republic","B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC"
"O. P. Kretzmann","B-PER I-PER I-PER"
"Federation of Norwegian Professional Associations","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
"He also works for BT Sport as an analyst .","O O O O B-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"`` Strollin ' '' ( Horace Silver ) - 7:53","O O O O O B-PER I-PER O O O"
"Moshe Gafni ( from 23 July 1990 )","B-PER I-PER O O O O O O"
"Considered the oldest residential property in Westchester County , New York .","O O O O O O B-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC I-LOC O"
"Museo di Storia Naturale di Venezia , Venice","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O B-LOC"
"Transformers : Prime '' ( 2014–present )","B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG O O O O"
"** ''The Bronx '' ( 2003 album )","O B-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG I-ORG"
